Idris Mustapha

SUMMARY

Dedicated developer offering background writing clean and well-planned code to produce various web projects. Contributed to full development process with continual support through design, testing, release and maintenance. Worked diligently to complete quality work to meet specifications and deadlines. Works great with team members under Agile and Scrum frameworks.

Highly-motivated employee with desire to take on new challenges. Strong worth ethic, adaptability and exceptional interpersonal skills. Adept at working effectively unsupervised and quickly mastering new skills.

EXPERIENCE

Johnsons Controls - Monitoring Call Center Agent

Toronto, ON • 04/2023 - Current

- Managed high-volume of inbound and outbound customer calls.
- Resolved customer inquiries, questions and concerns to consistently offer quality service and meet performance benchmarks.
- Handled customers effectively by identifying needs, quickly gaining trust, approaching complex situations and resolving problems to maximize efficiency.
- Maintained strong call control and quickly worked through scripts to address problems.
- Delivered fast, friendly and knowledgeable service for routine questions and service complaints.
- Managed customer expectations by clarifying needs, identifying options and recommending products and services.
- Met or exceeded call speed, accuracy and volume benchmarks on consistent basis.
- Conducted video surveillance and monitored security equipment at facilities to ensure optimal security.
- Documented incident reports according to customer and department requirements, maintaining accurate alarm handling procedures and interactions records.

HUGO TECHNOLOGIES, - Strategy and Transformation Analyst

Yaba, Lagos • 07/2022 - 12/2023

- Reviewed established procedures to assess areas in need of improvement.
- Implemented unique methods and methodologies, which helped reduce and resolve issues.
- Documented research findings and prepared polished reports highlighting results

CONTACT

musteidris@gmail.com 6476569695 Toronto, Ontario M1S2P1

SKILLS

- Proficiency in ReactJS, PHP, NodeJs, JavaScript, Java, Linux and Python
- Microsoft Office 365
- · Azure Active Directory
- Multi-Factor Authentication
- Azure Conditional Access
- · Problem-Solving Skills
- Documentation and Reporting
- Technical Support
- · CRM Software
- Troubleshooting and Diagnosis
- JIRA
- Scrum Methodology
- Databases
- AWS IAM
- Inbound and Outbound Calling

EDUCATION AND TRAININ G

Bachelor of Science: Zoology University of Lagos Yaba, Lagos • 10/2019

Associate of Science: Software Engineering Technician

and potential improvement strategies.

- Researched and led investigations into various areas to drive improvements and devise new processes.
- Assessed employees through on-site observation and interviews to determine strengths and weaknesses in work performance, methods and team functions.
- Devised new and improved records management programs to organize and protect data.
- · Prioritized and organized tasks to efficiently accomplish service goals.

Lenilabs - Software Developer / Technical Support Engineer Yaba, Lagos • 10/2018 - 12/2020

- · Analyzed solutions and coding fixes for software problems.
- Met with stakeholders, product teams and customers throughout system development lifecycle.
- Collaborated with cross-functional team to define features and build powerful and easy-to-use products and customer-facing workflow tools.
- Liaised with QA testers to perform testing meeting various parameters.
- Developed web applications using variety of engineering languages.
- Conducted full lifecycle software development from planning to deployment and maintenance.
- Engaged with user experience designers crafting clean interfaces with simple, intuitive interactions and functions for software package.

Konga - IAM Engineer Intern

Ikeja, Lagos • 06/2018 - 09/2018

- Utilized lean knowledge and tools to identify and assist with continuous improvement initiatives.
- Researched and analyzed customer design proposals, specifications, manuals and other data.
- · Understood and complied with safety regulations.
- Improved technical abilities by pursuing training and practical learning opportunities.

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- https://idrisportfolio-e3c77e31fca2.herokuapp.com/
- https://github.com/eedrisss?tab=repositories
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/idris-mustapha-81b147143/

Centennial College Toronto, ON

CERTIFICATIONS

- AWS IAM ,Coursera 2023.
- Technical Support
 Certificate Coursera 2021
- Data Analysis Certificate Coursera - 2022
- AWS Machine learning Foundations, Udacity - 2021
- Introduction to Cloud Computing, Udacity - 2020